Finding Aid for John Engler Papers, 1968-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Gubernatorial Papers, 1970-2003; 411 linear feet
  - Legal Division, 1991-2002; 18.4 linear feet
    - Topical Files, 1985-2002; 1.7 linear feet
      - Homeland Security Post-9/11, 2001-2002 (Box 182)
      - Kelly, John, malfeasance removal from the Board of Governors for Wayne State University, 2002 (Box 182)
      - Lottery--Political bingo miscellaneous correspondence, 1994-2002 (Box 183)
      - Office of Regulatory Reform, 1995-1999 (Box 183)
      - Privatization, 1992 (Box 183)
      - Product liability, 1995 (Box 183)
      - Public Service Commission, 1997-1999 (Box 183)
      - Redistricting--access to database, 2002 (Box 183)
      - Secretary of State--Bureau of Elections Proposal A, 1993-1994 (Box 183)
      - Secretary of State--Bureau of Elections Voter ID law (proposed legislation), 1997-1999 (Box 183)
      - Secretary of State--Emergency Interim Executive Succession Act, 1999 (Box 183)
      - Secretary of State--National Voter Registration Act, 1994-1995 (Box 183)
      - Secretary of State--Recall petitions, 1991-2001 (Box 183)
      - Secretary of State--Term limits proposal, 1991 (Box 183)
      - State Police--Towers, 1994-2001 (Box 183)
        (Mobile communication systems, Motorola)
      - Tesmer v. Granholm (Appointed appellate counsel), 2000-2001 (Box 183)
      - Tiger Stadium, 1995-1998 (Box 183)
      - Tort reform project, 1991-1997 (Box 183)
      - Transportation, misc., 1996-1998 (Box 183)
      - Veto, 1991 (Box 183)
      - Wayne County Airport suit, 2002 (Box 183)
    - Indians--State Tribal Affairs, 1993-2002; 1 linear feet
      - 2002 Government-to-Government Accord between the State of Michigan and the Federally Recognized Indian Tribes in the State of Michigan, Lansing, Michigan, October 28, 2002 (Box 183)
        (original document)
      - Air quality, 1996-2001 (Box 183)
      - Babbitt independent counsel, 2000 (Box 183)
        (Under seal of US Court of Appeals for the DC Circuit. Engler's aid was allowed to view portions of the independent counsel's sealed report that mentioned Engler. Memo summarizes his findings there.)
      - Battle Creek Casino, 2000 (Box 183)
      - Burt Lake Land Claim, 1993 (Box 183)
      - Casino construction permits, 1999 (Box 183)
      - Charlotte Beach settlement, 2001-2002 (Box 183)
      - Commission on Indian Affairs, 1998-2000 (Box 183)
      - Compact amendment to 4(D), 1996-1997 (Box 183)
      - Compact extension, 2001 (Box 183)
      - Compact negotiations, 1995-1997 (Box 183)
      - Compacts
        - Little River Band of Ottawa Indians, September 25, 1995 (Box 183)
        - Little River Band of Ottawa Indians, January 29, 1997 (Box 183)
        - Little Traverse Bay Bands of Odawa Indians, September 25, 1995 (Box 183)
        - Little Traverse Bay Bands of Odawa Indians, January 29, 1997 (Box 183)
        - Nottawaseppi Huron Tribe of Pottawatomie, January 29, 1997 (Box 183)
        - Pokagon Band of Pottawatomie Indians, January 25, 1995 (Box 183)
        - Pokagon Band of Pottawatomie Indians, January 29, 1997 (Box 183)
      - Environmental issues, 1999-2001 (Box 183)
      - Federal Indian Taxation, 1995 (Box 183)
      - Federal Recognition, 1992-1997 (Box 183)
      - Fishing: Archive materials, 1998-2002 (Box 183)
      - Florida Suit (Indian Gaming Regulatory Act), 1999 (Box 183)
      - Gaming, 1992-1996; 2 folders (Box 183)
      - Gaming compacts--Attorney General opinion, 1997 (Box 183)
      - Gaming compacts--New Tribes, 1998 (Box 183)
      - Gaming/Land holdings, 1994 (Box 183)
      - Gaming Litigation (Box 183)
      - General, 1994-1995 (Box 183)
      - Governors' Interstate Indian Council, 2002 (Box 183)
      - Grand River, 2001 (Box 183)
      - Grand Traverse Band/Turtle Creek Casino--Section 2719 application, 1999-2002 (Box 183)
      - Great Lakes Fishing Consent Decree, 1994-1999 (Box 183)
      - Greektown Casino, 1993-1994 (Box 183)
      - Gun Lake Band Casino, 2000-2002 (Box 183)
      - Gun Lake Band--Federal Recognition, 1997 (Box 183)
      - Hannahville Indian Community, 2001 (Box 183)
      - Indian Gaming Regulatory Act (IGRA) Negotiations Meeting, September 10, 1998 (Box 183)
      - IGRA amendments, 1995; 2 folders (Box 183)
      - Inland Hunting and Fishing Issues 1836 Treaty, 1995-2002 (Box 183)
      - Jobs Commission, 1996 (Box 184)
      - Keweenaw Bay Indian Community (KBIC) v. USA-Marquette Casino, 1995-2001 (Box 184)
      - Keweenaw Tribe, 1991-2001 (Box 184)
      - Land Acquisition General (Info., letters, articles, etc.), 1995-2001 (Box 184)
      - Legal challenges to 1998 gaming compacts, 1997-2002 (Box 184)
      - Legal Services Corp., 1993 (Box 184)
      - Legalized gambling, 1992 (Box 184)
      - Little Traverse Bay Bands (LTBB)--Early Opening dispute, 1999 (Box 184)
      - Loan assistance, 1997-2001 (Box 184)
      - Mapping of Indian Lands, 2000-2001 (Box 184)
      - Nottawaseppi Huron Band of Pottawatomie Indians, 1996 (Box 184)
      - Off reservation gaming, 1995-1997 (Box 184)
      - Oversight of gaming, 1997 (Box 184)
      - Perrier case, 2002 (Box 184)
      - Pokagon Band of Pottawatomie Indians, 1996 (Box 184)
      - Saginaw Chippewa audit, 1999 (Box 184)
      - Saginaw Chippewa Indian Tribe litigation, 1991-1993 (Box 184)
      - Sault Ste. Marie v. Engler compact litigation (Box 184)
      - Sault Ste. Marie Tribe, general, 1997-2000 (Box 184)
      - Seminole Case, 1996 (Box 184)
      - South Fox land swap, 2002 (Box 184)
      - State Law/Indian reservation issues, 1995-1996 (Box 184)
      - State/Tribal gaming negotiations, 1993 (Box 184)
      - Taxation disputes/negotiations, 1996-2002 (Box 184)
      - Tribal Judgment Fund Distribution, 1997 (Box 184)
      - Tribes & 800 MHz, 2002 (Box 184)
      - Tuition waiver, 1995 (Box 184)
      - Unemployment Act changes, 2001 (Box 184)
      - Wisconsin Pottawatomie, 1996-1997 (Box 184)
    - Correspondence of Legal Counsel and Deputy Legal Counsel, 1991-2002; 2 linear feet
      - Lucille S. Taylor, 1991-2002; 8 folders (Box 184)
      - Lucille S. Taylor (cont.), 1991-2002; 4 folders (Box 185)
      - Michael Gadola, 1991-1998; 6 folders (Box 185)
      - Office of Regulatory Reform, 1995 (Box 185)
      - Robert C. Steinman, 1991 (Box 185)
      - Deputy Legal Counsel, 1996-2002; 2 folders (Box 185)
      - Deputy Legal Counsel (cont.), 1996-2002; 7 folders (Box 186)
      - Other correspondence and memos, 1992-1995 (Box 186)
    - Redistricting
      - Redistricting, 2001-2002 (Box 186)
      - Michigan Court of Appeals 2000 Redistricting, 2001, 2000-2001 (Box 186)
    - Judicial Appointments, 1991-2002
      - Michigan State Bar Ratings, 1991-1999 (Box 187)
      - Judicial Appointment Decision Memos Supreme Court, Court of Appeals (Box 187)
      - Judicial Appointment Decision Memos Circuit Courts, 1991-2002; 4 folders (Box 187)
      - Judicial Appointment Decision Memos District Courts, 1991-2002; 4 folders (Box 187)
  - State Government Affairs, 1991-2002; 52 linear feet
    The primary mission of the State Government Affairs Division (52 lin. ft.) in the Engler administration was to coordinate the development and implementation of state governmental policy and programs. The SGA Director served as the principal liaison between the Governor's Office and the Cabinet Members, Department Directors, and Agency Heads on matters pertaining to development, analysis, and implementation of policy and programs. Individual policy coordinators were responsible for acting as liaisons between the Governor's Office and their assigned departments. The records in this series represent the best way to access the important policy decisions made during Engler's three terms.
    - Policy Division (Predecessor of State Government Affairs) and Senior Policy Advisor Dennis Schornack, 5 linear feet
      During the first term, the "Policy Office" (5 lin. ft.) was led by Dennis Schornack. During later administrations, Schornack became the Governor's Senior Policy Advisor, (though he also temporarily led the Department of Community Health). He was not then technically a part of the State Government Affairs office, but functionally aided in the generation and implementation of policy. His papers are therefore placed here in the State Government Affairs Division, for ease of access for the researcher. Schornack's "Governor Engler Correspondence" files for 1991-1994 are important documents for understanding policy decisions for the Governor's first term. Other important projects Schornack coordinated include "Annex 2001" which was a proposal to amend the Great lakes Charter to regulate the diversion of Great Lakes Water; the Michigan Commission on End of Life Care, the Michigan Commission on Genetic Privacy, the sale of the Michigan Biologic Products Institute (manufacturer of vaccines) and the development of the Thunder Bay National Marine Sanctuary and Underwater Preserve.
      - Senior Policy Advisor to the Governor Dennis Schornack, 1990-2002; 4.2 linear feet
        - Annex, 2001; 1999-2002
          - Annex, 2001; 1999-2002; 4 folders (Box 189)
            (Proposal to amend the Great Lakes Charter of 1985 to regulate diversion of Great Lakes Water)
          - Annex 2001 Ceremonial Documents, 2001 (Box 189)
        - Certificate of Need (CON), 1997-2000 (Box 189)
        - Governor Engler Correspondence, 1991-2002
          - Governor Engler Correspondence, 1991-2002; 12 folders (Box 189)
        - Michigan Commission on End of Life Care, 1999-2001
          - Michigan Commission on End of Life Care, 2000-2001 (Box 190)
          - End of Life Commission, 1999-2000; 7 folders (Box 190)
          - End of Life Commission Appointments, 1999 (Box 190)
          - End of Life Commission, Draft Final Report, April 19, 2001; 3 folders (Box 190)
          - End of Life Commission, Main File, 2000 (Box 190)
        - Michigan Commission on Genetic Privacy and Progress, 1997-2000
          - Genetics Commission Correspondence, 1997-2000 (Box 190)
          - Genetics Commission Executive Order, Transmittal Letter, etc., 1997 (Box 190)
          - Genetics Commission Report etc., 1999-2000 (Box 190)
          - Genetics Commission Working Documents, 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 190)
          - Genetics Commission Working Documents (cont.), 1997-1998; 1 folders (Box 191)
          - Genetics Legislation, 2000 (Box 191)
          - Genetics Press Clips, 1999 (Box 191)
        - Psychiatric Prison Consent Decree, 1991-2001
          - Psychiatric Prison Consent Decree, 1991-2001; 1991; 6 folders (Box 191)
        - Sale of the Michigan Biologic Products Institute (MBPI)
          - Executive Order 1995-25 (Box 191)
          - Executive Order Transmittal Letter, 1995 (Box 191)
          - Commissioners' Oaths of Office, 1996 (Box 191)
          - Michigan Biologic Products Commission (MBPC) By-Laws, undated (Box 191)
          - Resolutions 2-12, 1995-1996 (Box 191)
          - Public Acts 521 and 522, 1996 (Box 191)
          - Public Acts 8 and 9, 1998 (Box 191)
          - MBPC Meetings, 1996-1999; 7 folders (Box 191)
          - MBPC Meetings (cont.), 1996-1999; 2 folders (Box 192)
          - Chronology of Significant Events During MBPI Sale, 1997 (Box 192)
          - Standards of Employee Conduct Relative to Sale of the MBPI, undated (Box 192)
          - MBPC Correspondence, 1996-1997; 2 folders (Box 192)
          - Employee Letters to the Commission, November 1997 (Box 192)
          - MBPC Correspondence, 1998-2002; 2 folders (Box 192)
          - MBPI Asset Purchase Agreement, 1998 (Box 192)
          - MBPI Final Sale Documents, 1998; 5 folders (Box 192)
          - Escrow Account--Bank One, 1998 (Box 192)
        - Thunder Bay National Marine Sanctuary and Underwater Preserve, 1997-2002
          - Business Plan, 1999 (Box 192)
          - Dedication Ceremony, 2000 (Box 192)
          - Final Environmental Impact Statement/Management Plan (Box 192)
          - General Correspondence, 2000-2002; 2 folders (Box 192)
          - Governor's Input, undated (Box 192)
          - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) (Box 192)
          - Correspondence, 1997-1999; 2 folders (Box 192)
          - Correspondence (cont.), 1997-1999; 1 folders (Box 193)
        - Trash-City of Toronto, 2001 (Box 193)
      - Technology and Regulatory Affairs Policy Advisor Robert C. van Ravenswaay, 1990-1994; 0.8 linear feet
        - Advisory Group to the Governor on Mental Health and Corrections, Final Report, May 1991; 2 folders (Box 193)
          include background information
        - Ameritech Partnership, 1993 (Box 193)
        - Chief Information Officer Material, 1992-1994 (Box 193)
        - Commerce/Michigan Jobs Team, 1992-1993 (Box 193)
        - Michigan Government Television Network (MGTV), 1993-1994; 1 packets; 1 folders (Box 193)
        - Miscellaneous Notes from JME (Governor Engler), 1993-1994 (Box 193)
        - Tech Policy Material, 1992-1993; 1 packets; 1 folders (Box 193)
        - Transition Team Department of Mental Health--Team Report, 1990
          - Meeting Schedules and Notes, 1990 (Box 193)
          - Transition Materials, 1990 (Box 193)
    - Office of the Director, 1991-2002; 22.8 linear feet
      The "Office of the Director" files maintained by Dennis Schornack, Manny Lentine, and Brian DeBano contain Governor's signature correspondence on topics concerning state government agencies, arranged alphabetically by correspondent. The Director's "Department Issues," contain annual alphabetical files for of all the state departments. The key issues affecting those departments will be represented here, which makes these files an important resource. This subseries also contains the documents which proposed and implemented state departmental reorganizations and early retirement restructuring. The documents in the "Cabinet Vision Planning Retreat" subseries were created to prepare a platform for the 1998 campaign. Each department analyzed pending issues to discern and explain potential problem areas, accomplishments, and policy objectives for Governor's coming third term.
      - By year, alphabetical by correspondent, 1992-2001; 1.9 linear feet
        - A-P, 1992-1994; 18 folders (Box 194)
        - Q-Z, 1992-1994; 6 folders (Box 195)
        - A-Z, 1995; 2 folders (Box 195)
        - U.S. Congress, 1995 (Box 195)
        - A-Z, 1996 (Box 195)
        - A-Z, 1997 (Box 195)
        - A-Z, 1998; 2 folders (Box 195)
        - A-Z, 2000; 2 folders (Box 195)
        - A-Z, 2001; 8 folders (Box 195)
      - By drafter, 1994-2002; 1.5 linear feet
        - Gigliotti, Lisa, 1999-2002; 2 folders (Box 195)
        - Gigliotti, Lisa (cont.), 1999-2002; 6 folders (Box 196)
        - Ginster, Tom, 1994-2002; 8 folders (Box 196)
        - Harding, Kim, 2000-2002; 3 folders (Box 196)
        - Hare, Matt, 2000-2001; 6 folders (Box 196)
        - Hare, Matt (cont.), 2000-2001; 8 folders (Box 197)
        - Jenkins, Scott, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 197)
        - Ladd, David, 1998; 3 folders (Box 197)
        - Selleck, John, 1999-2000 (Box 197)
      - Department Issues, 1994-2002; 13.4 linear feet
        - 1994
          - Church Meetings/Issues
            - Flint Church Community, 1994 (Box 197)
            - Clergy Summit, 1995 (Box 197)
            - United Methodist Church, 1993-1994 (Box 197)
          - Information Network, 1993 (Box 197)
          - Labor
            - Michigan First, 1993-1994 (Box 197)
            - Job Training: Adult Education Alternative Training, 1992 (Box 197)
            - Michigan Jobs Commission
              - General, 1993-1994 (Box 197)
              - Business Ombudsman, 1992-1994 (Box 197)
          - Management and Budget
            - General, 1993-1994 (Box 197)
            - Privatization, 1993-1994 (Box 198)
          - State Employer, Office of
            - General, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 198)
            - State Employer, Office, Report and Recommendations: Committee to Review Departmental Suggestions Concerning Civil Service and Collective Bargaining Issues, March 12, 1992 (Box 198)
            - Drug Control Policy, Office of, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 198)
          - Mental Health, 1993-1994 (Box 198)
          - Military Affairs/Veterans, 1993-1994 (Box 198)
          - Natural Resources, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 198)
          - Public Service Commission, 1994 (Box 198)
        - 1st Series, 1995
          - Gas Tax, 1995 (Box 198)
          - U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, 1995 (Box 198)
          - Occupational and Professional Regulation, 1995 (Box 198)
          - Aging, 1995 (Box 198)
          - Agriculture, 1995; 3 folders (Box 198)
          - Agriculture--Office of the Racing Commissioner, 1995 (Box 198)
          - Attorney General, 1995 (Box 198)
          - Cabinet Council Mtg. (Box 199)
            (re: DNR pollution topics)
          - Civil Rights, 1995; 2 folders (Box 199)
          - Civil Service, 1995 (Box 199)
          - Commerce, 1995 (Box 199)
          - Corrections, 1994-1995 (Box 199)
          - Crime Bill Advisory Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 199)
          - Education, 1995 (Box 199)
          - Environmental Quality, 1995 (Box 199)
          - DEQ--Office of the Great Lakes, 1995 (Box 199)
          - Liquor Control Commission, 1995 (Box 199)
          - Military Base Conversions, 1995 (Box 199)
            (Re: Selfridge Army Garrison, Detroit Arsenal, Reserve Center Cadillac, Oscoda Wurtsmith, K.I. Sawyer Air Force Base)
          - Natural Resources, 1995 (Box 199)
          - Public Health, 1995 (Box 199)
          - State, 1995 (Box 199)
          - State Police, 1995 (Box 199)
          - Social Services, 1995 (Box 199)
          - DSS--Welfare Reform, 1995 (Box 199)
          - Transportation (Box 199)
          - Treasury (Box 199)
        - 1995-2nd Series
          - Commerce--Financial Institutions Bureau, 1995 (Box 199)
          - Commerce--Insurance Bureau, 1995 (Box 199)
          - Commerce--Public Service Commission, 1995 (Box 199)
          - Economic Development, 1993 (Box 199)
          - Empowerment Zone, 1995 (Box 199)
          - Jobs
            - Equal Employment Opportunity Paper, 1992 (Box 199)
              (William C. Whitbeck)
            - MI Jobs Commissioner, 1993 (Box 199)
            - Detroit Job Corps Center, 1992-1993 (Box 199)
            - MI Job Pac, 1994 (Box 199)
            - Workforce issues, 1993 (Box 199)
            - Statement of Work (Youth Apprenticeship), undated (Box 199)
          - Michigan Employment Security Commission
            - Michigan Job Pact, 1991-1995 (Box 199)
            - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 199)
            - Wagner-Peyser Funding, 1993-1994 (Box 199)
          - Michigan Agenda for Economic Growth, 1992 (Box 199)
          - Michigan Enterprise Zone Authority (EZA), 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 200)
            (Atlas Project)
          - National Center for Neighborhood Enterprise, 1991-1995 (Box 200)
          - Public Health, 1993-1995 (Box 200)
          - Public Service Commission, 1995 (Box 200)
          - Regional Development
            - Americana Foundation, undated (Box 200)
            - Southeast Michigan Council of Governments (SEMCOG), 1991 (Box 200)
          - State Employer, undated (Box 200)
          - Transportation, Legislative Issues, 1992 (Box 200)
          - Travel Bureau, 1995 (Box 200)
          - Treasury
            - Cut and Cap, 1991-1992 (Box 200)
            - Headlee Blue Ribbon Commission, 1994 (Box 200)
            - Personal Income, 1993 (Box 200)
          - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 200)
            (National Governor's Council correspondence)
        - 1996
          - Cabinet, 1996 (Box 200)
            (Memos from Lentine to the cabinet)
          - Agency Heads, 1996 (Box 200)
            (Memo from Lentine to all agency heads)
          - Wayne County Commissioners, 1996 (Box 200)
          - Agriculture
            - General, 1996 (Box 200)
            - Michigan State Fair, 1996 (Box 200)
              (Racing)
          - Attorney General (Box 200)
          - Civil Rights (Box 200)
          - Community Health
            (Formerly Dept. of Public Health)
            - General, 1995-1998; 2 folders (Box 200)
            - Office of Services to the Aging (Box 200)
            - Medicaid Issues, 1995-1996 (Box 200)
          - Community Service Commission, 1995 (Box 200)
          - Consumer and Industry Services
            (Formerly Dept. of Commerce)
            - General, 1995-1996 (Box 200)
            - Drug Control Policy, Office of (ODCP), 1996 (Box 200)
            - Insurance Commission, 1996 (Box 200)
            - Liquor Control Commission, 1996 (Box 200)
            - Financial Institutions Bureau, 1996 (Box 200)
            - Mobile Home Commission, 1996 (Box 200)
            - Public Service Commission, 1996 (Box 200)
            - Workers' Compensation Appellate Commission, 1996 (Box 200)
          - Corrections, 1996-1997 (Box 200)
          - Education
            - General, 1996-1997 (Box 200)
            - Implementation Plan for Charter School Program, 1996 (Box 200)
          - Environmental Quality (DEQ), 1995-1997; 2 folders (Box 200)
          - Environmental Quality (DEQ) (cont.), 1995-1997; 2 folders (Box 201)
          - Family Independence Agency (FIA)
            (Formerly Department of Social Services)
            - General, 1995-1997; 2 folders (Box 201)
            - Golden Rule, 1996 (Box 201)
              (Insurance litigation)
            - Project Zero, 1997 (Box 201)
            - Recovery of Overpayments, 1996 (Box 201)
            - State Clergy Summit Resource Directory, 1995 (Box 201)
            - Summer Food Service Program, 1997 (Box 201)
            - The Urban Institute: Assessing the New Federalism, 1997 (Box 201)
            - Welfare Re-write, 1995 (Box 201)
            - Women, Infants and Children (WIC), 1996 (Box 201)
            - Work First Program, 1995-1998 (Box 201)
          - Labor, Dept. of
            - General, 1996 (Box 201)
            - Michigan Jobs Commission, 1995-1996; 5 folders (Box 201)
            - Michigan Employment Security Commission (MESC) Employer Survey, 1995 (Box 201)
            - Michigan First, 1995 (Box 201)
          - Management and Budget (DMB)
            - General, 1996 (Box 201)
            - Lottery, 1995 (Box 201)
          - Michigan International Trade Authority, 1995 (Box 201)
          - Office of Children's Ombudsman, 1996 (Box 201)
          - Military Affairs, 1995-1998 (Box 201)
          - Natural Resources, 1995-1997; 2 folders (Box 201)
          - State, Dept. of, 1996 (Box 201)
          - State Employer, Office of, 1996 (Box 201)
          - State Police (MSP), 1996-1997 (Box 201)
          - Tobacco Lawsuit, 1996 (Box 202)
          - Transportation (MDOT), 1994-1996 (Box 202)
        - 1997
          - National Governors' Association, 1995-1997 (Box 202)
          - Cabinet, 1997 (Box 202)
          - Agency Heads, 1997 (Box 202)
          - Project Staff, 1997 (Box 202)
          - Misc.
            - General, 1997 (Box 202)
            - John Engler Technology Message (Box 202)
            - Corrections Advisory Group (Box 202)
            - Fire Marshal Executive Order (Box 202)
            - Legal History Project (Box 202)
          - Civil Rights, 1998 (Box 202)
          - Community Health
            - General, 1998 (Box 202)
            - Aging (OSA), 1996-1997 (Box 202)
            - Drug Control Policy (ODCP), 1997 (Box 202)
            - First Care Health Plan, 1996 (Box 202)
          - Consumer and Industry Services
            - General, 1997; 2 folders (Box 202)
            - Associated Builders and Contractors of Michigan--Andy Anuzis, 1996-1997 (Box 202)